Mauro Velez

Game Developer | Unity | C# | C++ | UE4

New York, NY - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Mauro-Velez/6ddd2b93e50dead4

Hey my name is Andrew. I really love to code. I spend a lot of my time working on school projects or solo projects. There's something amazing about solving a problem and seeing your hard work show up on the screen. Like when i was able to implement the google autocomplete api to allow someone to search for their property. Then showed their property using the google maps api. It was a simple problem but the fun part about it was creating something real that customers will find useful.

A lot of my experience is in C++, C#, Unity, Unreal, Java, html, css, JavaScript, and React. In total i have 3 Years experience in Software and Game Development. If you're interested in hiring me go ahead and call or email me.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Game Development Intern | Unity Developer

IGT - Reno, NV - June 2017 to Present

- Created Editor Scripts to help artist streamline the UI Creation.
- Parsed a word document that contained rules for a game.
- Helped save artist 30-50 hours per game.

Technologies: C#, Unity

Game Developer

Puppetry Arts - New York, NY - June 2017 to Present

- · Created my own pixel based system in Unity for drawing.
- Allowed a kid to save the drawings they create.
- Improved previous UI to stop tearing and pixilation.

Technologies: C#, Unity, Photoshop

Web Development Intern

TaskEasy - Salt Lake City, UT - March 2017 to June 2017

- Implemented the Google Maps API and Google Places API.
- Adjusted to a new coding language in less than 1 week.
- Worked closely with designers to create pixel perfect UI.

Technologies: React, Java, mysql, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Game Developer | UI Developer

Burst Fighters - Enterprise Project - January 2017 to March 2017

- · Leveraged Photoshop skills to create intuitive UI.
- Designed an equipment system for users to apply to their party.
- Developed a tutorial system using user feedback.

Technologies: C#, Unity, Photoshop, Maya

Tools Programmer

Imagine - Solo Project - September 2016 to March 2017

- Implemented Runtime Compiled C++ a feature fewer than 20 game engines have implemented.
- Created a Content Browser, Hierarchy, and tool bar.

Technologies: C++, Qt, OpenGL

Game Developer

Ruins of the Old God - Student Project - June 2016 to August 2016

- Improved FPS by 280% by pooling game objects & using layers.
- · Created different attack patterns for the Als.
- In charge of Music acquisition and User testing.

Technologies: C#, Unity, Photoshop

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Software and Game Development in Software and Game Development

Neumont University - Salt Lake City, UT 2017

SKILLS

.NET (1 year), C# (2 years), Git (2 years), Trello/Jira (2 years), C++ (2 years), Unity (2 years), Unreal Engine 4 (1 year), QT (1 year), Maya (1 year), Photoshop (4 years)

LINKS

http://andrewvelez.net

https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-velez